[
    {
        "type":"nat",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "from":"20",
        "to":"21",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"Discrete Mathematics",
        "SubTopic":"Shortest Distance"
    },
    {
        "type":"mcq",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "optionA":"A",
        "optionB":"B",
        "optionC":"C",
        "optionD":"D",
        "optionE":"E",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"Engineering Mathematics",
        "SubTopic":"Matrices",
        "correctAnswer":"C"
    },
    {
        "type":"nat",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "from":"20",
        "to":"21",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"COA",
        "SubTopic":"K-map"
    },
    {
        "type":"mcq",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "optionA":"A",
        "optionB":"B",
        "optionC":"C",
        "optionD":"D",
        "optionE":"E",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"Engineering Mathematics",
        "SubTopic":"Matrices",
        "correctAnswer":"C"
    },
    {
        "type":"nat",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "from":"20",
        "to":"21",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"COA",
        "SubTopic":"Soft"
    },
    {
        "type":"mcq",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "optionA":"A",
        "optionB":"B",
        "optionC":"C",
        "optionD":"D",
        "optionE":"E",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"Computer Network",
        "SubTopic":"udp",
        "correctAnswer":"C"
    },
    {
        "type":"nat",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "from":"20",
        "to":"21",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"COA",
        "SubTopic":"K-map"
    },
    {
        "type":"mcq",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "optionA":"A",
        "optionB":"B",
        "optionC":"C",
        "optionD":"D",
        "optionE":"E",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"Engineering Mathematics",
        "SubTopic":"Broze",
        "correctAnswer":"C"
    },
    {
        "type":"nat",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "from":"20",
        "to":"21",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"COA",
        "SubTopic":"Straight"
    },
    {
        "type":"mcq",
        "question":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "optionA":"A",
        "optionB":"B",
        "optionC":"C",
        "optionD":"D",
        "answer":"https://www.fillmurray.com/640/360",
        "topic":"Engineering Mathematics",
        "SubTopic":"Matrices",
        "correctAnswer":"A"
    }
]